<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://localhost:4000/thoughts/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/thoughts/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/thoughts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-01-04T23:22:29-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/thoughts//</id><title type="html">Jake Zimmerman</title><subtitle>A collection of my thoughts and longer-form writings.</subtitle><author><name>Jake Zimmerman</name></author><entry><title type="html">On Stripe</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/thoughts/on-stripe/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Stripe" /><published>2017-01-04T22:53:51-06:00</published><updated>2017-01-04T22:53:51-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/thoughts/on-stripe</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/thoughts/on-stripe/">&lt;section&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interning at Stripe was one of the best experiences of my career. Now that I’ve chosen to return there after graduation, I’d like to share some of my thoughts. Stripe is a great company, founded on solid engineering discipline, with a great future. I strongly encourage those who have the chance to work at Stripe to do it—any critical feedback found here is given with the hope that it will help make Stripe an even better place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’d also like to give the usual disclaimer: this is just my opinion&lt;span&gt;&lt;label for=&quot;sn-1&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;&gt;&amp;#8853;&lt;/label&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;checkbox&quot; id=&quot;sn-1&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;marginnote&quot;&gt; If I’ve learned one thing about HCI, it’s that “the user is not like me.”&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The key words here are “my” and “opinion.” These are my views, tainted by my background, shaped by my experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;newthought&quot;&gt;I’ll be honest: I came in to Stripe&lt;/span&gt; utterly unfit to answer questions posed by my friends like, “Oh, you’re interning at Stripe? What do they do?” An innocuous question sure, but equally difficult for me to answer. It wasn’t until my first day that I learned the answer. I’m really passionate about what Stripe does; it’s both worthwhile in the long run and engaging on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what is Stripe? If you ever get the chance to meet with someone on the PR team, they might say something like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stripe is a software platform for building an internet business. Stripe helps companies like Lyft, Kickstarter, Facebook, and others sell to anyone, anywhere, and in new ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is heavily steeped in PR rhetoric, but nonetheless does a good job of setting the stage. There’s a lot of meaning squished into those two sentences, so let’s un-squish it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stripe is a software platform.&lt;/strong&gt; It’s software that enables other software. But what &lt;em&gt;kind&lt;/em&gt; of software does it enable?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stripe is for building an internet business.&lt;/strong&gt; Stripe’s software aims to simplify the process of conducting business online. This is purposefully broad, but for example, Stripe helps business accept payments, keep track of customers, analyze fraud, simplify subscriptions, and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stripe has big-name customers.&lt;/strong&gt; This isn’t just some random startup. Stripe is the go-to choice for many established companies, in addition to smaller upstarts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stripe helps others sell to anyone, anywhere, and in new ways.&lt;/strong&gt; Companies in in more than 20 countries and customers around the world can transact using Stripe. Stripe also focuses on how to make complicated problems simple, leading to new, better products for businesses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s “what Stripe is,” but that’s not “what excites me about Stripe.” I don’t run an internet business, certainly never one headquartered overseas. Nevertheless, Stripe appeals to me individually.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stripe puts developers first. While Stripe’s product is for businesses, it’s the software developers at that business who directly consume the product. Those developers take significant time and effort to build their app or product on top of the software platform that Stripe curates. Being a developer, I can’t help but smile that a company has it’s priorities this far aligned with my peers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a two-way street as well. It’s awesome to work at a company that my peers recognize as a valuable and reputable tool for building the things they want to. When I tell my friends I work at Stripe, I say it like a badge of honor, because I feel like I’ve contributed back to my community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In line with this, Stripe’s business intentions are clear. Stripe earns money on every transaction. It’s in Stripe’s best interest to help businesses grow, because Stripe can’t profit without first helping other businesses to profit. This is quite different from how many other internet companies work. Some make money by advertising, which usually&lt;span&gt;&lt;label for=&quot;sn-2&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle sidenote-number&quot;&gt;&lt;/label&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;checkbox&quot; id=&quot;sn-2&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;sidenote&quot;&gt;Let it be known I have a rather antagonistic view of advertising in general.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; amounts to a company stealing it’s users personal information. Other companies use marketing campaigns to trick customers into buying something that’s somewhat useful, but which they might not really need. On the other hand, Stripe provides a real need and profits along side them, not in spite of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This idea of helping businesses grow isn’t just an afterthought: it’s another of Stripe’s core values. Phrased a little differently, Stripe arms upstarts to compete with well-established contenders. Companies like Amazon have the size and sway to chat with a bank, set up an account, and procure the ability to charge credit cards. The college freshman making a business from a laptop in a dorm room might not have that luxury. Stripe enables upstarts like this to start accepting payments from day one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s a pretty cool image. The internet should be a place where anyone can carve out their own homestead, rather than only those with an army big enough to fight for them. By arming upstarts, Stripe empowers future generations to use the internet to change their little (or big!) part of the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;newthought&quot;&gt;So for a number of reasons&lt;/span&gt;, Stripe’s mission excites me. The future Stripe sees for the internet is a future I’d be proud to say I helped create. But Stripe’s vision is only the foundation upon which a company culture is built. Stripe’s culture inspired personal growth while encouraging teams to work better together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, the people at Stripe were&lt;span&gt;&lt;label for=&quot;sn-3&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;&gt;&amp;#8853;&lt;/label&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;checkbox&quot; id=&quot;sn-3&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;marginnote&quot;&gt; I don’t mean to imply that this &lt;em&gt;is no longer&lt;/em&gt; the case! While I write this, writing this, I am not &lt;em&gt;currently&lt;/em&gt; at Stripe; I’m addressing my experience.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; ridiculously talented, pervasively thoughtful, and humble. By “ridiculously talented,” I’m talking about the feeling where you walk into a meeting and feel like the least talented person there—every time. To exemplify “pervasively thoughtful,” at company-wide all hands meetings, it seemed like everyone was two steps ahead with an insightful question. And throughout it all people at Stripe were humble. Certainly each person is different, but I saw some degree each of these traits in everyone at Stripe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the top of it all are two confident and passionate co-founders: John and Patrick Collison. In a company full of talented and thoughtful people, this duo topped the charts. Richard Hamming talks of “first-class” people in his seminar &lt;em&gt;You and Your Research&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;label for=&quot;sn-4&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle sidenote-number&quot;&gt;&lt;/label&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;checkbox&quot; id=&quot;sn-4&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;sidenote&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cs.virginia.edu/~robins/YouAndYourResearch.html&quot;&gt;You and Your Research&lt;/a&gt;, by Richard Hamming. &lt;em&gt;Worth the read.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Whenever I think of the kinds of people Hamming describes in this talk, I immediately think of these two, because hearing them speak inspires a sense of drive to become better. Just, truly great men.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking from a broader perspective, the culture at Stripe is fueled by a sense of urgency. While Stripe has been around longer than most startups, it’s by no means well established. While I don’t see it flopping any time soon, people at Stripe still act as though they have something to prove. This sense of urgency stems from a fear of Stripe not reaching it’s full potential. A fear of not bringing Stripe’s dream for the internet to fruition. People worked hard without overworking themselves due to this air of urgency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;newthought&quot;&gt;Stripe’s mission and core values&lt;/span&gt; resonate with me strongly as worthwhile and challenging in the large, but also as something I can personally identify with. The group of people Stripe has chosen to see this plan through is talented and rigorous, and is headed by two great men. Overall, I’m excited to be a part of Stripe, and I look forward to seeing where we go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name>Jake Zimmerman</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>
