<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://jez.io/thoughts/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://jez.io/thoughts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-11-18T23:07:59-08:00</updated><id>https://jez.io/thoughts/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Jake Zimmerman</title><subtitle>A collection of my thoughts and longer-form writings.</subtitle><author><name>Jake Zimmerman</name></author><entry><title type="html">Social. Private. Open. Pick three.</title><link href="https://jez.io/thoughts/on-leaving-facebook/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Social. Private. Open. Pick three." /><published>2017-09-27T01:58:31-07:00</published><updated>2017-09-27T01:58:31-07:00</updated><id>https://jez.io/thoughts/on-leaving-facebook</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jez.io/thoughts/on-leaving-facebook/">&lt;section&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve uninstalled Facebook and Facebook Messenger from my phone, and am no longer going to be checking the Facebook or Messenger websites. I still want to make it easy for people to get ahold of me, which you can &lt;a href=&quot;#contacting-me&quot;&gt;find more about below&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This has been a long time in the making for me. Almost 2 years ago I restricted my use of Facebook to 30 minutes a day. Shortly after that I uninstalled the Facebook app from my phone. Around a year ago I killed my News Feed with a Chrome extension. I spend no time using the core Facebook product anymore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The only thing left to go was Messenger. I used Messenger almost exclusively in college both for chatting with friends but also for reaching out to people I happened to meet. Today, I’ve finally uninstalled Messenger from my phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s rare right now for people to actively leave Facebook, but a handful of people wish they could or are trying to. Since it’s so uncommon, here’s why &lt;em&gt;I’ve&lt;/em&gt; made this choice:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section id=&quot;facebook-abuses-privacy&quot; class=&quot;level2&quot;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Facebook Abuses Privacy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s well-known that Facebook’s ad-based revenue model involves meticulously tracking users’ behavior throughout Facebook and all across the Internet. Facebook nominally allows users to control their privacy settings, but these overwhelmingly focus on interpersonal privacy. We have far less control over Facebook selling our personal information. This has been written about extensively, but here are some links:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.salimvirani.com/facebook/&quot;&gt;Get your loved ones off Facebook.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This article is one of the most comprehensive articles of Facebook’s malpractices, covering considerations of privacy, politics, advertising, and much more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://stallman.org/facebook.html&quot;&gt;Reasons not to use Facebook&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This post by Richard Stallman is a bit exhausting, but at least it’s in character. Stallman brings forth a laundry list of points; each one is easy to dismiss individually, but they’re eerie when taken in sum.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Privacy is a sneakily important topic.&lt;span&gt;&lt;label for=&quot;sn-0&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;&gt;&amp;#8853;&lt;/label&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;checkbox&quot; id=&quot;sn-0&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;marginnote&quot;&gt; George Orwell’s &lt;em&gt;1984&lt;/em&gt; is actually a really fascinating book, and I’d highly recommend it. Orwell weaves a compelling story of personal struggle, political commentary, forbidden love, and distopian conclusions that leaves no question why it’s still a classic.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; When you have it, it’s easy to forget what kind of world it would be if we gave it up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section id=&quot;facebook-is-a-threat-to-the-open-internet&quot; class=&quot;level2&quot;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Facebook Is a Threat to the Open Internet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With regard to the Internet, I’m definitely an idealist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Governments of the Industrial World, you weary giants of flesh and steel, I come from Cyberspace, the new home of Mind. On behalf of the future, I ask you of the past to leave us alone. You are not welcome among us. You have no sovereignty where we gather.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– John Perry Barlow, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eff.org/cyberspace-independence&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Declaration of the Independence of Cyberspace&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Barlow wrote this letter in 1996—over 20 years ago. We owe a debt of gratitude to all those who worked to make the Internet a tool that anyone can use. Nominally, Facebook’s goal of a more interconnected world is in line with this original vision. But counterintuitively, much of what Facebook is working towards tears down the progress we’ve already made.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To read more about this, I suggest &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/matter/the-web-we-have-to-save-2eb1fe15a426&quot;&gt;The Web We Have to Save&lt;/a&gt;. After being pardoned from Iranian imprisonment for being an open web advocate, the author gives his perspective on what happened to the Internet over the 6 years he was away from it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not too late to stop this. The Internet was made to be open, and we can still make sure that it is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section id=&quot;we-have-the-technology&quot; class=&quot;level2&quot;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;We Have The Technology&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t want the effects of my choices to infringe my friends and family’s freedoms. I need to make myself available online in as many ways as possible—with open, private systems as the default. But by continuing to use Facebook, I make the default implicitly closed-off and privacy-invasive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are lots of fascinating new technologies in this space which I’d love to see become the default:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://signal.org/&quot;&gt;Signal&lt;/a&gt; is a messaging app that neither compromises on privacy nor social sharing—and uses some fascinating new technologies to do so. Signal encrypts messages by default, their client and server code is open source, and they’re actively trying to rely less on trust. They’re even finding innovative ways to empower users to &lt;a href=&quot;https://signal.org/blog/private-contact-discovery/&quot;&gt;own their own social graphs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span&gt;&lt;label for=&quot;sn-1&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;&gt;&amp;#8853;&lt;/label&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;checkbox&quot; id=&quot;sn-1&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;marginnote&quot;&gt; This post actually left me mind blown at how rigorously they’re thinking about how to solve these hard problems.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This post describes how they’re working on solving problems that people didn’t thing possible in the realm of private social networking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://solid.mit.edu/&quot;&gt;Solid&lt;/a&gt; is a project by Tim Berners-Lee and MIT to give data ownership back to those who use web apps, as opposed to those who run them. Imagine Facebook, but where all your posts, all your images, and your friend list belongs to you, rather than Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://keybase.io/&quot;&gt;Keybase&lt;/a&gt; is pioneering new experiences around encryption, with a goal of making encryption the default in all software. For more about how this works, read &lt;a href=&quot;https://keybase.io/blog/keybase-chat&quot;&gt;Introducing Keybase Chat&lt;/a&gt;. Keybase Chat is friendlier for crypto newcomers and power users alike, and they’re shipping new features at an impressive pace. They’ve released Keybase Teams (a fancy, encrypted Slack-alike app), Keybase Filesystem (encrypted shared files right in the file system), and even encrypted git (for sharing code privately).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section id=&quot;but-jake-the-hypocrisy&quot; class=&quot;level2&quot;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;But Jake, the hypocrisy!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When talking about this before, people have brought up some hard questions that I’ll pre-emptively address here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section id=&quot;couldnt-you-say-the-same-things-about-google&quot; class=&quot;level3&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;“Couldn’t you say the same things about Google?”&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’re right. Between Search, Chrome history, Gmail, Maps, Docs, YouTube, and the fact that I browse the Internet signed in, Google probably knows more about me than Facebook!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That being said, I’m not at a spot right now where I can leave Google. Running a personal mail server turns out to be not that easy. Google Docs is near ubiquitous for collaborating on document drafts, with no high-quality, open replacement. I could switch from Chrome to Firefox, from Google Search to Duck Duck Go, or take a number of other measures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I’d like to think through these changes rigorously first. For example, if I naively switched from Chrome to Firefox, but didn’t change my search engine, have I changed anything? Even though right now the focus is on switching away from Facebook, that doesn’t mean that I’m ignoring everything else. I just want my decisions to be cost-effective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section id=&quot;do-you-really-not-support-anything-facebook-does&quot; class=&quot;level3&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;“Do you really not support anything Facebook does?”&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I actually have a huge amount of respect for many engineers from Facebook. They’re pioneering scaling web services, have helped train thousands of people on how to design usable web interfaces, and are one of the best companies for releasing open source software. I’m personally a huge fan of React, Flow, and Immutable.js.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regardless of what I do in the short term, Facebook will continue to train engineers to scale large systems, write maintainable software, and contribute to open source. Even if Facebook’s core product went under, Facebook’s existing open source projects would live on through their public communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With regard to open source specifically, what we really want is to find better ways to build and grow open source communities. Mozilla and Redhat are fascinating case studies for companies releasing open source software, but not everyone can follow this model. Patreon and Kickstarter have helped fund &lt;em&gt;individual maintainers&lt;/em&gt;, and there are similar efforts to grow support at the community level. Even switching from corporate ownership to corporate donations would improve certain communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section id=&quot;are-you-saying-that-facebooks-service-provides-zero-value&quot; class=&quot;level3&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;“Are you saying that Facebook’s service provides zero value?”&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like with any service, you pay a cost&lt;span&gt;&lt;label for=&quot;sn-2&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;&gt;&amp;#8853;&lt;/label&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;checkbox&quot; id=&quot;sn-2&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;marginnote&quot;&gt; To be clear: I’m talking about both monetary and social costs throughout this section.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to use Facebook’s service, and receive value in return. I judged what I gave up and what I got back and realized I was net negative in terms of value.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the most part, this deficit comes from the high cost, as opposed to low value—Facebook still provides a lot of value. Even for Facebook users that only use Messenger there’s a lot of value; when you throw into the mix the value people get from features like being able to share posts and participate in groups, Facebook’s value prop gets even larger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main value I got from Facebook was sending messages. Given that there are other ways to send messages at a lower cost, this choice makes sense for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section id=&quot;contacting-me&quot; class=&quot;level2&quot;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Contacting Me&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going forward, here’s how you can reach me:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;by SMS/iMessage: (414) 460-3435&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;on Signal: (414) 460-3435&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;on Keybase: &lt;span class=&quot;citation&quot; data-cites=&quot;jez_&quot;&gt;@jez_&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;on Telegram: (414) 460-3435&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;by email: jake at zimmerman dot io&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is definitely a case of “the perfect is the enemy of the good.” None of these is a silver bullet, but each is strictly better than Facebook in terms of privacy or openness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The web was originally built for the people. Along the way, we sacrificed individual freedom for collective adoption. We’re now posed to take back those freedoms while without risking privacy or openness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What are we waiting for?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- vim:tw=72
--&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name>Jake Zimmerman</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Stripe</title><link href="https://jez.io/thoughts/on-stripe/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Stripe" /><published>2017-01-04T20:53:51-08:00</published><updated>2017-01-04T20:53:51-08:00</updated><id>https://jez.io/thoughts/on-stripe</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jez.io/thoughts/on-stripe/">&lt;section&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interning at Stripe was one of the best experiences of my career. Now that I’ve chosen to return there after graduation, I’d like to share some of my thoughts.&lt;span&gt;&lt;label for=&quot;sn-0&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;&gt;&amp;#8853;&lt;/label&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;checkbox&quot; id=&quot;sn-0&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;marginnote&quot;&gt; I’d also like to give the usual disclaimer: this is just my opinion. These are my views, tainted by my background, shaped by my experiences. Any critical feedback that I give here I do with the hope that it will help make Stripe an even better place.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Stripe is a great company, founded on solid engineering discipline, with a great future. I strongly encourage those who have the chance to work at Stripe to do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;newthought&quot;&gt;I’ll be honest: I came in to Stripe&lt;/span&gt; utterly unfit to answer questions posed by my friends like, “Oh, you’re interning at Stripe? What do they do?” An innocuous question sure, but equally difficult for me to answer. It wasn’t until my first day that I learned the answer. I’m really passionate about what Stripe does; it’s both worthwhile in the long run and engaging on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what is Stripe? If you ever get the chance to meet with someone on the PR team, they might say something like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stripe is a software platform for building an internet business. Stripe helps companies like Lyft, Kickstarter, Facebook, and others sell to anyone, anywhere, and in new ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is heavily steeped in PR rhetoric, but nonetheless does a good job of setting the stage. There’s a lot of meaning squished into those two sentences, so let’s un-squish it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stripe is a software platform.&lt;/strong&gt; It’s software that enables other software. But what &lt;em&gt;kind&lt;/em&gt; of software does it enable?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stripe is for building an internet business.&lt;/strong&gt; Stripe’s software aims to simplify the process of conducting business online. This is purposefully broad, but for example, Stripe helps businesses accept payments, keep track of customers, analyze fraud, simplify subscriptions, and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stripe has big-name customers.&lt;/strong&gt; This isn’t just some random startup. Stripe is the go-to choice for established companies, in addition to smaller upstarts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stripe helps others sell to anyone, anywhere, and in new ways.&lt;/strong&gt; Companies in more than 20 countries and customers around the world can transact using Stripe. Stripe also focuses on how to make complicated problems simple, leading to new, better products for businesses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s “what Stripe is,” but that’s not “what excites me about Stripe.” I don’t run an internet business, certainly never one headquartered overseas. Nevertheless, Stripe appeals to me individually.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stripe puts developers first. While Stripe’s product is for businesses, it’s the software developers at that business who directly consume the product. Those developers take significant time and effort to build their app or product on top of the software platform that Stripe curates. Being a developer, I can’t help but smile that a company has its priorities this far aligned with my peers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a two-way street as well. It’s awesome to work at a company that my peers recognize as a valuable and reputable tool for building the things they want to. When I tell my friends I work at Stripe, I say it like a badge of honor, because I feel like I’ve contributed back to the developer community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In line with this, Stripe’s business intentions are clear. Stripe earns money on every transaction. It’s in Stripe’s best interest to help businesses grow, because Stripe can’t profit without first helping other businesses to profit. This is uncommon in internet companies. Some make money by advertising, which usually&lt;span&gt;&lt;label for=&quot;sn-1&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle sidenote-number&quot;&gt;&lt;/label&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;checkbox&quot; id=&quot;sn-1&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;sidenote&quot;&gt;Admittedly, I have a rather antagonistic view of advertising in general.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; amounts to a company stealing its users personal information. Other companies use marketing campaigns to trick customers into buying something that’s useful, but which they might not really need. On the other hand, Stripe provides a real need and profits alongside them, not in spite of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This idea of helping businesses grow isn’t just an afterthought: it’s another of Stripe’s core values. Phrased a little differently, Stripe arms upstarts to compete with well-established contenders. Companies like Amazon have the size and sway to chat with a bank, set up an account, and procure the ability to charge credit cards. The college freshman making a business from a laptop in a dorm room might not have that luxury. Stripe enables upstarts like this to start accepting payments from day one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s a pretty cool image. The internet should be a place where anyone can carve out their own homestead, rather than only those with an army big enough to fight for them. By arming upstarts, Stripe empowers future generations to use the internet to change their little (or big!) part of the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;newthought&quot;&gt;So for a number of reasons&lt;/span&gt;, Stripe’s mission excites me. The future Stripe sees for the internet is a future I’d be proud to say I helped create. But Stripe’s vision is only the foundation upon which company culture is built. Stripe’s culture inspires personal growth and a drive to achieve great things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The people at Stripe were&lt;span&gt;&lt;label for=&quot;sn-2&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;&gt;&amp;#8853;&lt;/label&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;checkbox&quot; id=&quot;sn-2&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;marginnote&quot;&gt; I don’t mean to imply that this &lt;em&gt;is no longer&lt;/em&gt; the case! While writing this, I am not &lt;em&gt;currently&lt;/em&gt; at Stripe; I’m addressing my experience.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; ridiculously talented, pervasively thoughtful, and humble. By “ridiculously talented,” I’m talking about the feeling where you walk into a meeting and feel like the least talented person there—every time. To exemplify “pervasively thoughtful,” at company-wide all-hands meetings, it seemed like everyone was two steps ahead with an insightful question. And throughout it all people at Stripe were humble. Certainly each person is different, but these traits stood out among people at Stripe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the top of it all are two confident and passionate co-founders: John and Patrick Collison. In a company full of talented and thoughtful people, this duo topped the charts. Richard Hamming talks of “first-class” people in his seminar &lt;em&gt;You and Your Research&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;label for=&quot;sn-3&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle sidenote-number&quot;&gt;&lt;/label&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;checkbox&quot; id=&quot;sn-3&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;sidenote&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cs.virginia.edu/~robins/YouAndYourResearch.html&quot;&gt;You and Your Research&lt;/a&gt;, by Richard Hamming. &lt;em&gt;Worth the read.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Whenever I think of the kinds of people Hamming describes in this talk, I immediately think of these two, because hearing them speak inspires a sense of drive to become better. Just, truly great men.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s important to me who I surround myself with. I was reminded this summer that “we are 5% ourselves, and 95% our cohort.”&lt;span&gt;&lt;label for=&quot;sn-4&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle sidenote-number&quot;&gt;&lt;/label&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;checkbox&quot; id=&quot;sn-4&quot; class=&quot;margin-toggle&quot;/&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;sidenote&quot;&gt;Qasar Younis of Y Combinator mentioned this at an event for YC interns. He made some wild remarks that evening, but this one is spot on.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The people at Stripe embody the type of person I would like to become.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking from a broader perspective, the culture at Stripe is fueled by a sense of urgency. While Stripe has been around longer than most startups, it’s by no means well established. People at Stripe still act as though they have something to prove, even though they’ve come a long way. They work hard without overworking themselves, trying to prove themselves every day. This urgency arises from a fear that Stripe might not reach its full potential—a fear of not achieving Stripe’s dream for the internet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;newthought&quot;&gt;I want this dream to come true.&lt;/span&gt; I want to become the kind of person that abounds at Stripe. Stripe’s plan is worthwhile and challenging, and the group of people at Stripe are talented and thoughtful enough to see it through. Overall, I’m excited to be a part of Stripe, and I look forward to seeing where we go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name>Jake Zimmerman</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>